Pearl,
لؤلؤة،
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
Miss,
يفتقد،
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
Shh.
صه.
Pearl,
لؤلؤة،
go get the doctor.
اذهب واحضر الطبيب.
Remember not to reveal his identity.
تذكر عدم الكشف عن هويته.
Yes.
نعم.
Be careful.
كن حذرا.
You didn't listen to me
أنت لم تستمع إلي
and acted without permission.
وتصرفت بدون إذن.
Do you know what the consequences are?
هل تعرف ما هي العواقب؟
I'm also thinking about the great cause of the Holy Lord.
أنا أفكر أيضًا في قضية الرب العظيم.
If Qin Molin doesn't die in a single day,
إذا لم يمت تشين مولين في يوم واحد ،
the great cause will be hard to achieve,
سيكون من الصعب تحقيق السبب العظيم ،
Should I reward you?
هل يجازيك؟
As loyal as you are,
مخلص مثلك ،
I dare not,
لا أجرؤ،
Is Qin Molin
هل تشين مولين
dead or alive?
ميت او حي؟
I don't know,
لا أعلم،
after Qin Molin was stabbed,
بعد طعن تشين مولين ،
He escaped.
هرب.
No trace.
لا أثر.
It's no use
غير صالح
keeping a disobedient dog.
الاحتفاظ بكلب عاص.
Clean him up.
نظفه.
Continue to trace Qin Molin's whereabouts.
استمر في تتبع مكان تشين مولين.
I want to see a person alive or a corpse dead.
اريد ان ارى شخصا حيا او جثة ميتة.
also
أيضًا
Inform Hearing Murder
إبلاغ جريمة السمع
that I want to meet him.
أريد مقابلته.
Yes
نعم
Take care, doctor.
اعتني بنفسك يا دكتور.
Take care.
يعتني.
My Lady,
سيدتي،
didn't you go out to look for materials?
ألم تخرج للبحث عن مواد؟
Why did you bring His Majesty back?
لماذا أعدت جلالة الملك؟
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
And he got hurt.
وقد أصيب.
Is it another plot of rebellion?
هل هي مؤامرة تمرد أخرى؟
It's so dangerous.
إنه أمر خطير للغاية.
I'd better stay out of it.
من الأفضل أن أبقى خارجها.
No way.
مستحيل.
After all, he saved me twice.
بعد كل شيء ، أنقذني مرتين.
We can't just leave him in disarray.
لا يمكننا تركه في حالة من الفوضى.
Gosh.
يا الهي.
Also,
أيضًا،
what's wrong with His Majesty's injury?
ما خطب جلالة الملك؟
I don't know.
لا أعلم.
I ran away from the palace,
هربت من القصر
because I wanted to live a peaceful life.
لأنني أردت أن أعيش حياة هادئة.
But I still couldn't escape.
لكن ما زلت لا أستطيع الهروب.
This must be God's will.
يجب أن تكون هذه إرادة الله.
By the way, Miss,
بالمناسبة يا آنسة ،
you haven't eaten yet, have you?
لم تأكل بعد ، أليس كذلك؟
I'll get you something to eat.
سأحضر لك شيئا لتأكله.
Go cook some porridge.
اذهب طهي بعض العصيدة.
He can drink it when he wakes up.
يمكنه أن يشربه عندما يستيقظ.
Yes.
نعم.
Tell me
أخبرني
Why can't I run away from you?
لماذا لا استطيع الهروب منك
No, no, no.
لا لا لا.
This scene is simply inviting people to commit crimes.
هذا المشهد ببساطة يدعو الناس لارتكاب جرائم.
This room is too stuffy.
هذه الغرفة خانقة للغاية.
I need to get some fresh air.
أنا بحاجة للحصول على بعض الهواء النقي.
Su Jinxia, what are you thinking about every day?
سو جينشيا ، ما الذي تفكر فيه كل يوم؟
Is she injured?
هل هي مصابة؟
But he's so handsome.
لكنه وسيم جدا.
Master,
يتقن،
I didn't expect that,
لم أتوقع ذلك ،
How could Her Highness show up there?
كيف يمكن أن تظهر سموها هناك؟
Why am I confused?
لماذا أنا في حيرة من أمري؟
Why did His Majesty leave?
لماذا غادر جلالة الملك؟
I don't know
لا أعرف
what to do with the plan, either. What should I do?
ماذا تفعل بالخطة أيضًا.  ماذا يجب أن أفعل؟
Come out.
يخرج.
Cancel the plan.
قم بإلغاء الخطة.
In my lifetime,
في حياتي،
I can't believe I saw my master
لا أصدق أنني رأيت سيدي
being carried away by a woman.
حمله امرأة.
Me,
أنا،
I won't be silenced, will I?
لن أسكت ، أليس كذلك؟
Her body is so warm.
جسدها دافئ جدا.
Be careful.
كن حذرا.
Slow down.
ابطئ.
It's like the temperature of my mother when I was a child.
إنها مثل درجة حرارة والدتي عندما كنت طفلاً.
You knew you would be in danger,
كنت تعلم أنك ستكون في خطر ،
but you still chose to save me.
لكنك ما زلت اخترت أن تنقذني.
She's really different from others.
إنها مختلفة حقًا عن الآخرين.
It's not your fault
انها ليست غلطتك
that the empress had an accident.
أن الإمبراطورة تعرضت لحادث.
How is it going?
كيف الحال أو كيف تسير الأمور؟
Did the snake get out of its hole?
هل خرج الثعبان من جحره؟
The snake has come out of the cave,
خرج الأفعى من الكهف ،
Master.
يتقن.
Shouldn't we go back to the palace?
ألا يجب أن نعود إلى القصر؟
I was seriously injured,
لقد أصبت بجروح خطيرة ،
so of course I have to stay with Her Highness.
لذلك بالطبع يجب أن أبقى مع صاحبة السمو.
Take good care of your injury.
اعتن جيدًا بإصابتك.
Seriously injured,
مصاب بجروح خطيرة،
Master,
يتقن،
if the doctor comes later,
إذا جاء الطبيب لاحقًا ،
Your wound is about to heal.
جرحك على وشك الشفاء.
Don't think I didn't see you sweating yourself
لا أعتقد أنني لم أراك تتعرق بنفسك
with your internal energy,
مع طاقتك الداخلية ،
I tricked Her Highness into wiping your sweat.
لقد خدعت سموها لكي تمسح عرقك.
Inform Eunuch Li.
أبلغ الخصي لي.
Ask him to send me
اطلب منه أن يرسل لي
to Zizhu Residence tomorrow morning to visit the empress,
إلى Zizhu Residence صباح الغد لزيارة الإمبراطورة ،
It will take a few days for the news to be announced.
سيستغرق إعلان الأخبار بضعة أيام.
Send the memorial to Zizhu Villa,
أرسل النصب التذكاري إلى Zizhu Villa ،
and bring it to me for review.
وإحضاره إليّ لمراجعته.
Boss,
رئيس،
I heard from Pearl,
سمعت من بيرل ،
Your friend got hurt?
اصيب صديقك؟
Yes.
نعم.
My friend is injured.
صديقي مصاب.
Just friends, right?
مجرد أصدقاء ، أليس كذلك؟
Men or women,
رجال أو نساء ،
there's never been a man
لم يكن هناك رجل قط
around the empress.
حول الإمبراطورة.
Madam,
سيدتي،
what is Qin Molin up to?
ماذا يفعل تشين مولين؟